[{"answer": "Winklevoss is fine.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "I mean it should be technically, isn't it?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, it was definitely -- we had to remind ourselves, even though we knew that there were some CGI effects and -- after a while, you're watching the movie and you kind of forget that it's one guy playing two people.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "That must have been weird, wasn't it, watching one guy play both of you?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "There's definitely a lot of uncertainty.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Did you want to go and see it?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Harvard.edu.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "How is that different from MySpace or Friendster?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "There's so many things to think.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "Honestly?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "We see --", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Horrible?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "We certainly see a person who is where he is today absolutely because we approached him with our idea, our business plan, and two years of worth of work.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Sure, I mean he's intelligent.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Didn't he just come along and go, I really like that idea, but I've got a better one?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "That's one way of putting it.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "A cheat?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "The guy that looks over your shoulder and nicks some of your best lines?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "What we agreed to and what we got are two different things.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "And is that part of our ongoing dispute, then?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "I mean if the company is worth X billion dollars and, you know, people decided you were telling the truth, and your idea had been stolen, why didn't you get $4 billion?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Well, this is a very principled --", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Is he -- again, devil's advocate, I mean, aren't you guys also just in this for the money now?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "It's a good question, I understand that sentiment.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Why don't you let it go?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well, it -- money is inextricably tied to the principle.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "It's not about money for you?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Both have to be -- I'll tell you why both are important.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "What's more important?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Were you one-hit wonders?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Well, w happened was that when Mark launched the Facebook, when we were completely blindsided by it, we launched our site later, but because of the damage, we were late to market.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "We've got a couple of ideas in the works.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Have you had another great idea?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "Or are you worried about me stealing it?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "It's doing well.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "How is that doing?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I'd say probably in the millions.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "What's it worth do you think?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "But you go to Harvard, you get trained to be an attack dog in business?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Within the rules.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Isn't just attack dog speak?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "In effect we did, we first learned about Facebook and Mark Zuckerberg launching it by reading the Harvard student newspaper.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Did that moment happen?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "We were pretty shocked.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "And what was your first reaction?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "We spoke to him at the mediation in 2008.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to him?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "You haven't spoken to him in, what, three years?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "He clearly at this moment doesn't care.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Why should I care?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "You think so?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "He hasn't any of that?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "First of all, we got screwed because we place trust and confidence in a partner.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Have you read to that?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "In what --", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "What do you think of Eduardo?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Did he get screwed as well do you think or not?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "We don't know.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "How much did he end up with?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, that's a different -- we shouldn't be conflated with Eduardo.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Again I say to you, I mean, how sorry are we supposed to feel for you guys?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Do you use Facebook?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Not as ironic if we weren't on it because again --", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Quite ironic, isn't it?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Well, we worked that out because the guys who -- who originated the idea would be -- you would think that would be the ones who would be able to take part in it.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "How do you work that out?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "It's north of 1,000.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "How many friends do you have?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Tyler.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Who's got more?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Just more diligent at it.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Maybe.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Nicer guy?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "That's a tough question.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Who gets more women?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Well, but back to we got all of this money.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "I mean they must be cueing up, are they?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Piers, it's dangerous to make assumptions about anybody's life.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Well, the immediate future is training for London 2012.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What's the future going to hold for you?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "We're going to try.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "And can you win there?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "As long as -- again as long as it's fair play --", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What do you do if Mark Zuckerberg suddenly pops up in a rival boat that's just a little bit better than yours?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Are you going to sue him?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Not -- I mean, I think we've done a very good job of compartmentalizing.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "How often do you think about him a day?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I wouldn't call it a career.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "It's not a bad career, though, is it?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "What we want is a fair resolution.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "How much money do you want?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, it's not what we have now.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "How much do you want?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "A mediation where --", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "$100 million?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "We're not going to -- we're not going to answer that question.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Two hundred?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "$65 million?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "We're reasonable people.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "No one wants to hear anymore about Mark and you think, how much?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "If I invite Mark Zuckerberg on this show with you, would you come on?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I think the public doesn't know the complete story yet.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Final question, do you have the public are on your side or on Mark Zuckerberg's?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "No, it's not true.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "That's not true, is it?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "I'm -- you know, a better personality.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Where do you think that you're different from that character that was portrayed in the film?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I have to tell time.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Do they?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "You say you beat the odds.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "Need to be able to tell time, you know?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "You know, coming from where I came from, you know, the environment I was in, you know, being taken in by my family, the Tuohy family, that doesn't happen every day.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "How did you beat the odds?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I owe them quite a bit, because they didn't have to do what they did, taking somebody in to their family, you know, coming from where I came from.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "So how much do you think you owe the Tuohys?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "The road would have been a little bit tougher, but, you know, growing up, I always said that -- you know, since I was 13, I'm going to get out.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "You think you would have made it anyway?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "No, I was not going to be a cycle.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "You were not going to be sucked down by the system you were born into?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Right now, I'm the only one.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "What percentage of kids that you grew up with got out?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "You know, like you say, you never understand it fully.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "If you were telling me how tough it's been, what were the toughest moments for you?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "You know, some things you have to force yourself to, you know, put behind you in order to move on.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "If I remember, I don't think so.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "The baby was killed?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "You know, the relationships -- you know, it's not like it used to be.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Do you talk to her anymore?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "You know, I -- she was a product of her environment.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Do you think that was the root of all the problems for her?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "I really don't know.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "What do you think she thinks of your success now?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "I never heard it from her.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "But she hasn't told you that?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "You know, after you try to help a person for so long, you know, they have to want to help them self.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Why did you stop talking?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "No, she said it a number of times before I finally told her \"I love you\" back.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Do you remember the first time you heard those words?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "It will always be hard for me.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "Or do you find it hard?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "Yeah, I saw the movie.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "You went to see it?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "You know, yeah, in a fact, because people don't have a movie made about them every day.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "What was that like, weird?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "That's zero out of a billion.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "You don't get that every day, do you?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "I haven't met any of them.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "Have you met Sandra?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "She loved it.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "Did she?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "She's starting to take on the personality in the movie, actually.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "That's got to be a dream come true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "Has it damaged your relationship with the Tuohys at all, the attention, the movie, the books, and everything?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "You know, I just want to send a message out that you don't have to be saved by a wealthy white family.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "What would you say to them to try and achieve what you've achieved?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "I play him.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "You still want to beat him, right?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "Well, they talk a lot.", "docId": "110212pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "As the rose between two thorns in this particular interview, what were they like, these two, to work for, these two heavily egoed movie stars?", "qSentId": 810}]